





Summary

Jump to Section

Experience of 8.5 years in Information Technology.

I am currently implementing projects on multiple public clouds with IAC, deploying SaaS and PaaS products, accomplishing CI/CD with DevOps tools, and leading the operations team. I am proficient in cloud deployments, migrations, containerization, and architecting cloud environments.

I am AWS and ITIL certified with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

Sabre as Senior Software Systems Engineer Feb 2019 to Till Date

Working on AWS, GCP, Kubernetes, Docker, Ansible, Jenkins, Git, Linux, Zabbix, AppDynamics, Rally, Jira.

Mercedes-Benz as Senior Systems Engineer Aug 2016 to Feb 2019

Worked on projects for migration of applications to Cloud, On-Premise Servers to AWS, maintenance of Linux Servers, infrastructure configuration, performance-monitoring/tuning & application optimization.

IBM as Senior Operations Specialist Sep 2015 to Aug 2016

Performed day-to-day infrastructure operations & batch processing

Altran Technologies as Engineer - Systems and Networks Jan 2013 to Sep 2015

As a Data Center Engineer and Enterprise IT Administrator, performed data centers management operations such as disaster recovery management, server patching and hardening.

247 Customer as Interactive Social Media Advisor May 2012 to Jan 2013

Provided technical support on Linux systems.

^ Back to Top

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
AWS, EC2, ALB, Cloud Formation		
S3, Route 53		
(App Engine, Compute engine		
Kubernetes Engine		
Cloud Storage, Cloud Deployment Manager		
Kubernetes, Jenkins, Linux		
Shell Scripting		
Ansible		0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				
Kannada				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.